YYeTs人人影视字幕组出品
更多原创字幕翻译 请登陆www.YYeTs.com
■
时间轴：godwuwen
后期： 孤帆  字幕总监： YY
■
翻译： Vero  阿蘅阿蘅  猫中之王  独醉
后期： 渔夫  字幕总监： YY
■
校对： YY    后期：渔夫   字幕总监： YY
老爸老妈浪漫史
第八季  第四集
孩子们  当马修叔叔和莉莉阿姨
Kids, once your Uncle Marshall and Aunt Lily
为小马文找好保姆后
found a nanny for baby Marvin,
他们为五个月以来的第一次夜晚外出  兴奋不已
they were excited for their first night out together in five months.
我们也是
And so were we.
老妈  老爸
Mama. Dada.
现在  这里没有
Ah, so, now that there's no
哭闹的宝宝让我们分心
screaming baby to distract us,
-说说你们各自的近况吧  -对啊
- what have you guys been up to lately? - Yeah.
这可是个一言难尽的问题
This was a surprisingly loaded question.
自从马文出生以来
You see, right after Marvin was born,
莉莉和马修颁布了一项新规定
Lily and Marshall had issued a decree.
新规定  除非你们的问题在8分或以上
New Rule.You can't come to us with any issue
否则不要来找我们
unless it's an eight or higher.
而我们也在努力遵守
And we were doing our best to abide.
泰德  你和维多利亚进展如何
Ted, how are things going with Victoria?
我爸说了个超好笑的笑话
My dad made the funniest joke.
他说我逃婚既然是因为你
He said that since you're the reason I left the wedding,
那他为婚礼支出的7万美元  你来还
you owe him the $70,000 he paid for it,
不然你就惨了
or else.
他平常可没这么有趣哟
You know, he's not usually funny like that.
前景不明朗  但算不上8分
Not promising, but not an eight.
一切顺利
Everything's great.
罗宾  你和尼克怎么样了
And Robin, how's everything with Nick?
终于准备好踏上摩托之旅了吗
Finally ready for a ride on the bike?
说我吗
Who? Me?
出发吧  大老爹[出自电影《冒牌老爸》]
Let's ride, Big Daddy.
太帅了
Oh, yeah.
老娘喜欢
Mama likey.
罗宾  在这边
Robin, over here.
这车才环保
Eco-friendly.
玉米动力车
She runs on corn.
简直让人性致全无  但算不上8分
Totally lady bone killer, but not an eight.
一切顺利
Everything's great.
那巴尼呢  近况如何啊
And how are things for the old Barnacle?
算不上8分
Not an eight.
她撑死了才6分  6.5分吧
At best, she was a six, six and a half.
滚完床单后  也就值4分吧
More like a four by the time I was done with her.
自己跟自己击个掌吧
Mental self-five.
一切顺利
Everything's great.
敬期待已久的马修和莉莉重返麦克伦酒吧
To long-awaited MacLaren's return of Marshall and Lily.
我太怀念这里了  好了  我们该走了
I've missed this. Okay. We got to go.
什么  你们才刚到啊
W-what? You just got here.
我特意为你们空出了一整晚
I cleared my whole night for you guys.
我甚至连约炮电话都没带
I didn't even bring my booty-call phone.
抱歉  但我们真的需要些私人时间
Oh, I'm sorry, but we just really need some time to ourselves.
我保证很快会再聚的
I promise we'll hang out soon.
-再见了各位  -拜
- See you guys. - Bye.
约炮约炮约炮  炮遍全世界 *
* Booty, booty, booty, booty rocking everywhere
约炮约炮约炮 *
* Booty, booty, booty, booty
好像我真会把它留在家里似的
Yeah, like I'm going to leave this at home.
我是巴尼・斯丁森  请为我的"神雕"指路
Barney Stinson. How may I direct my penis?
能出来透透新鲜空气真好
It is so nice to be out in the fresh air.
你闻到了吗
You smell that?
这尿的味道终于不是马文的了
That's the smell of urine that isn't Marvin's.
天啊  我超想那个气味
Oh, God, I miss that smell.
我原以为我们会一刻不停地惦记着马文
You know, I thought we'd spend the whole time worrying about Marvin,
但能出来透透气
but it's actually nice to be out
-享受下生活真不错  -是啊
- in the world, living life. - Yeah.
死神随时都会降临
Death is all around us.
那股子尿味刚突然变强了
Wow, that urine smell just got a lot stronger.
你们五个月以来  第一个自由的夜晚
So, you guys spent your first night out in five months,
就是坐在家里为你们的死亡做计划
sitting at home planning for your own deaths?
对  我们发现了一个帮人立遗嘱的网站
Yeah, we found this Web site that helps you make a will.
假如你不幸去世...
In the event of your death... Ooh!
抱歉
I'm sorry.
只是想到这个真的很伤心
It-it's just-just real sad to think about.
我知道
Oh, I know.
假如你不幸去世...
In the event of your death...
好了  不如这样
Okay, no, you know what?
我们从一些简单的条目做起
Let's just start with something easy.
请输入你的邮编
Please enter your zip code.
我们再也不会收到邮件了
We'll never get mail again.
我一直安慰莉莉  这一切都是假设
I keep reassuring Lily that this is all hypothetical.
相对而言  纽约是非常安全的
Relatively speaking, New York City is very safe.
拜托  电梯故障  井盖爆炸
Please, faulty elevators, exploding manhole covers,
因爱生恨的老公
jealous husbands.
这地方简直是验尸官的天堂
This place is a coroner's paradise.
抢劫升级成杀人的案件更是数不胜数
They are way more likely to eat it in a mugging gone wrong.
一周前你们的街区就发生了两起凶杀案
There was a double hommy on your block like a week ago.
午餐的时候  在扫描机上看见的
Caught it on the scanner during lunch.
拿刀子捅啊
Knife job.
当时的场面真是惨不忍睹啊
Guy made a real mess of it too.
话说回来
Anyway,
我们后来来到挑选监护人的环节
then we got to the section about picking a guardian.
有的夫妻会选一位自己的父母作为监护人
Sometimes couples choose one of their parents as a guardian.
这样简单多了
That makes it simple.
就我妈了
My mom.
你妈
Your mom?
我妈怎么了
What's wrong with my mom?
你是不是...
Are you...
45分钟后
好吧  行了
Fine. All right.
不把马文交给我亲爱的母亲
Marvin won't go to my loving mother.
但他总得有个去处吧
But he's got to go to somebody.
好吧
Fine.
我妈妈怎么样
What about my mom?
你妈
Your mom?
拜托
Um, excuse...
78分钟后
好吧
Fine.
不给我妈
Not my mom.
我爸爸呢
What about my dad?
你爸
Your dad?
1分钟后
好吧  他出局了
Okay, yeah, he's out.
等等  你知道谁最合适吗
Wait a minute. You know who could be good?
我哥哥马库斯
My brother Marcus.
他是个好爸爸
He's like a great dad.
你还记得他的圣诞卡片吗
Do you remember his Christmas card?
圣诞快乐
马库斯  莎拉
马丁  马库斯二世
除了牛仔裤  马库斯确实是个好爸爸
Questionable denim choices aside, Marcus is a good dad.
如果要寄养马文  家人是最好的选择
I guess if Marvin has to go to anyone, it should be family.
好的  很好
Okay, great.
好
Okay.
马库斯  近来好吗
Marcus, hey, how's it going?
老子好得很  臭小子
Pretty freaking sweet, buttwipe.
我把一切东西收拾好
I packed up all my crap, I said,
告别了莎拉和孩子们
"See ya" To Sarah and the kids,
终于在"寻欢作乐二号店"
and I finally got my dream job
得到了梦寐以求的调酒师工作
as a mixologist down here at Carnalism 2.
等等
Hold on.
有个白痴想用租来的潜水通气管吸大麻
Some punk's trying to use his snorkel rental as a bong.
拜托  你大麻放太多了吧
You be packin' that bowl too tight, mon.
所以我们现在还是没找到监护人
So, now we don't have a guardian.
作为你的挚友
You know, as your best friend,
如有需要让我来抚养马文  荣幸之至
if called upon, I'd be honored to raise Marvin.
如果你们想马文生活在  用旗杆晾内裤的环境中
If you want him to be raised by his underwear on a flagpole,
那就选泰德吧
Ted's your guy.
如果你们想让他成为欺负书呆的恶霸
If you want him pulling the chord on some other nerd's panties,
那选我准没错
I'm your guy.
我会教他如何成为了不起的人物
I'll teach that kid how to be awesome
这是你和莉莉永远教不会的
in ways you and Lily never could.
这将成为传...
It's going to be legend...
等等  算了  不等了
...wait for it, no, I won't wait for it
小马文也等不及了
and neither should little baby Marvin,
所以你俩最好现在就死了算了
so maybe it's better if you two just die right now...
...奇
...dary.
莉莉和马修最漫长的一周开始了
And so began the longest week of Lily and Marshall's lives.
改编自儿歌《Old McDonald Had a Farm》
麦当劳兄有农场  便宜了兄弟 *
* Bro McDonald had a farm, E-I-E-I-bro
农场里面有小妞 *
* And on that farm he had some chicks
便宜了兄弟 *
* E-I-E-I-bro
一美妞在东  一傻妞在西 *
* With a hot chick here and a dumb chick there...
改编自儿歌《Let your kite fly high》
兄弟  兄弟  划起你的兄弟船 *
* Bro, bro, bro your broat
轻轻划向酒吧 *
* Gently to the bar
发现浪女  喝上十杯...  *
* Hit on sluts, then do ten shots and...
改编自儿歌《The Wheels on the Bus》
车上的咪咪  抖啊抖 *
* The boobs on the bus go up and down
上下抖  左右抖 *
* Up and down, up and down
车上的咪咪  抖啊抖 *
* The boobs on the bus go up and down
一路抖过城 *
* All through the town.
你以为用婴儿车就能贿赂他们吗
You think you can bribe them with a stroller?
傻子  他们已经有一个了
They already got one, fool.
这不是婴儿车  罗宾
Oh, this is no stroller, Robin.
我称之为"兄弟车"
I call it the Broller.
来  看看里面
Go ahead. Look inside.
看不懂  什么都没有
I don't get it. I don't see anything.
那是  不过爸爸懂
Yeah, but Papa does.
那是罗宾的咪咪吗
Those Robin's boobies?
当性感辣妹弯腰来看你的孩子时
When new nubile hotties lean in to inspect your bundle of joy,
你也可以看她的那对奶子
you can inspect their bundles of joy.
"兄弟车"
The Broller.
天啊  我真是个天才发明家
God, I come up with a lot of good stuff.
大伙儿
Hey, guys, hey... Hey.
莉莉和我想请你们到楼上来
Lily and I need you to come upstairs.
这是个很重要的决定
This is an important decision
我们不能让你们幼稚的竞争
and we can't have you constantly interrupting us
不断打扰我们的生活
with this childish competition.
所以我们要来一场
Which is why we're going to make it
正式的比赛
an official competition!
"争夺教父母"大赛
We're going to play Who Wants to Be a Godparent?
广告之后  马上回来
Right after this word from our sponsors.
他为什么对着一面墙讲话
Why is he talking to the wall?
你们就用这个选出  谁是马文的监护人啊
Wait, this is how you're going to choose a guardian for Marvin?
那不如让我们参加三人搏斗铁笼赛
I mean, why don't you just put us in a three-way cage match
谁赢就归谁不得了
and go with whoever's left standing?
我们也想过  但是罗宾有压倒性的优势
We talked about that, but it gave Robin an unfair advantage.
伙计们  其实我们也很难做出抉择
Yeah, you see, guys, we were really struggling with this decision.
一路抖过城 *
* All through the town.
亲爱的  我知道他们最近
Babe, I know these guys have been
-有点夸张了  -才有点吗
- a little over the top lately. - A little?
不过为了以防万一  我们还是得选个监护人
But we still have to pick a guardian just in case.
万一什么
In case of what?
别逼我说出来
Don't make me say it.
说吧  我能接受  说吧
Say it. I can handle it. Say it.
万一我们死了
In case we die.
你还真说得出口
How can you even say it?
然后我就在想怎么去处理
And then I thought what do you do
我有个老婆一直在哭
if you got a wife who won't stop crying,
有三个傻蛋一直在贿赂自己
three idiots who won't stop bribing you,
还有一个人见人爱的制胜绝招
and a universally beloved skill for gamesmanship?
于是我想了一堆监护人该做的事
You take a bunch of guardianship scenarios,
写在转轮上
throw them on a wheel,
给老婆买一条昂贵的裙子  不然她不参加
buy your wife an expensive dress, so she'll participate.
老娘又貌美如花了
I'm pretty again.
最重要的是  我只是想
Bottom line is I just wanted
让"万一我和莉莉死掉..."这个想法
to make the idea of me and Lily dying...
变得有趣
fun.
现在  请各就各位  我们要开始了
Now, if you'll step behind your podiums, we'll get started.
各位选手
Contestants,
比赛规则如下
here's how the game works.
莉莉会转动转轮  先别动
Lily will spin that wheel. Not yet.
指针指向育儿问题时
When it lands on a parenting issue,
你们将各自阐述会如何处理
you'll each describe how you would handle it with Marvin.
分数最高的选手将成为
The contestant with the highest score gets to be
马文的教父或教母
his godparent.
准备好了吗  很好  莉莉
Ready to play? Great. Lily,
转动转轮
spin that wheel!
听着  热情度也会影响你们的得分
Okay, now, see, um, enthusiasm will factor into your scores.
我再说一次
So, I say again:
莉莉  转动
Lily, spin...
转动转轮
Spin that wheel!
我们的死亡
Our demise.
巴尼  你要怎么向小马文解释
Barney, how would you explain to little Marvin
-我们不在人世的原因  -太残忍了
- why we're not around anymore? - No.
很简单  我只要把我的泡妞金句
Easy, all I'd have to do is change a few words
改几个词就可以了
to one of my classics with the ladies.
世界总统安排你的父母
The President of the World has called your parents away
去执行一项机密的太空任务
on a super-secret space mission.
为了地球的安危  你再也见不到他们了
For the sake of the planet, you will never see them again.
收拾好你的玩具  和爸比说晚安吧
Now pick up your toys and say good night to Daddy.
真好  最后一句不改也适用
What do you know? That last line stays the same.
评委意见
Judges?
罗宾  你会怎么做呢  记住
Okay, Robin, what would you do, and remember,
"世界总统安排你的父母
"President of the World called parents away
去执行一项机密的太空任务"已经有人用过了哦
for a super-secret space mission" has already been taken.
我爸对我从不拐弯抹角  一向实话实说
Well, my dad was always upfront and honest with me,
所以我也会这样
so that's how I would be.
好了  孩子  你给我听好了
All right, kid, here's the deal with the deal.
你爸妈已经玩完了
Your mom and dad are done-ski.
扑通一声摔下地铁站台
Belly-flopped off a subway platform.
你妈被地铁碾开了花
Mom busted open like a pinata.
你爸残留的部分  在医院苟延残喘了几天
What was left of your dad hung around for a few days.
总之  生命仪器关了  器官也捐了
Anyway, plug's pulled. Organs donated.
长话短说  我就是你新妈妈了
Long story short: I'm your new mommy now.
节哀顺便吧
Sah-wish!
我本来是想留着当摆设的
Well, I was saving these for the showcase,
现在只好  莉莉宝贝  你看
but here. Hey, Lily, look, baby,
情侣表哦
his-and-her watches.
泰德  你有何高招呢
Ted, the category's all yours.
我的做法是
Okay, here's what I would say.
马文  要解释你父母的去向
Well, Marvin, explaining where your parents are
并不容易
isn't gonna be easy.
就算是我  莉莉和马修最好的朋友
Even I-- Lily and Marshall's best friend
有着近20年的深厚友情
for almost 20 years--
也无法轻松地完成这事
will have a hard time doing it.
但我知道有个人  特别擅长这种事
But I do know a guy who's very good at this sort of thing.
恐龙教授
Professor Infosaurus!
你好啊  小调皮
Hey, there, squirt!
死亡虽然不幸  但却无法避免
Death is a difficult yet unfortunate certainty.
很好
Good enough!
这一轮是泰德赢
Ted wins the round!
太好了  太好了  你们等着吧
Yes! Yes! You'll see.
恐龙教授肯定大受孩子们的欢迎
Professor Infosaurus will be a big, big hit with children.
是不是啊  孩子们
Isn't that right, kids?
我们继续
Moving on.
惩罚
"Discipline."
"当马文拿了其他小孩的玩具  你会怎么做"
"How would you handle Marvin taking another kid's toy?"
巴尼  你来
Barney?
小菜一碟
That's easy.
我要向儿童机构举报你
I'm calling Child Services.
别着急嘛
Wait for it.
除非你把玩具还给小朋友  否则我要没收
I'll return your $1,900 alligator-skin belt
你那条价值1900元的鳄鱼皮皮带
when you return that toy.
在此期间  你就用这条丑陋无比
Until then, you can wear this
半黑半棕的双面用皮带吧
disgusting black-and-brown reversible belt.
哭屁啊  我和你一样不喜欢这条皮带
Hey, I don't like it any more than you do!
泰德  你会如何惩罚马文呢
Ted, how would you discipline little Marvin?
我绝对严格
I would be firm.
公平  但不失严格
Fair, but firm.
好了  以后不准看电视
You, sir, just lost your television privileges.
好吧  可以看电视  但是不准看暴力节目
Okay, you can watch TV, but nothing violent.
好吧  可以看暴力节目
Okay, it can be violent,
但不洗碗不准看
but you have to do the dishes first.
好吧  碗我来洗  电视你看
Okay, I'll do the dishes, you watch TV.
我们弄点冰激凌吃  好不好
Let's go get some ice cream! Come on!
但冰激凌不准撒糖屑
But no sprinkles.
-罗宾  你呢  -好吧  可以撒糖屑
- Robin? - Okay, sprinkles.
我将贯彻我爸的做法  严厉教育法
Um, I would do what my dad did: tough love.
小子  知道我要送你去哪吗
You know where you're headed, chief?
英属哥伦比亚省是加拿大的一个省
英属哥伦比亚男童军校
The British Columbia Military School for Boys.
当然  你本身是男孩
Of course, you're actually a boy,
所以你至少不用剃掉满头秀发
so at least you won't have to shave off all your hair
也不用把你的女生衣服  扔进油桶里烧掉
and burn your "Girlie" clothing in an old oil drum
烧的时候  你爸还站在旁边
while your father stands there
在火焰中冲你哈哈大笑
and laughs at you through the flames!
往事不堪回首啊
Oh, my God!
这一轮是罗宾赢
I think that Robin wins this round
因为我们都爱她
because we love her
而且她现在很安全  对吧
and she's in a safe space, right, guys?
-罗宾最重要  -绝对是
- Robin matters! - Yay! Totally.
同情分只能算一分哦
Now, that's just one point, right?
莉莉
Lily.
转轮  转起来
A spin... that... wheel!
两性知识
"Birds and Bees."
巴尼  "你会如何向小马文
Barney, "How would you teach young Marvin
传授人性本能呢"
about the facts of life?"
你会爱死阿姆斯特丹的  老弟
You're gonna love Amsterdam, little bro.
荷兰阿姆斯特丹是性自由之都
以开放的性态度和性文化著称
这一轮巴尼出局
Okay, Barney's out of this round.
泰德  你会如何进行"两性之谈"呢
Ted, how would you handle "The talk"?
那时马文也算半个成年人了
Well, Marvin would be a young adult,
不能摆出居高临下说教的样子
so you wouldn't want to talk down to him.
但可以用别的方式让他理解
But that doesn't mean you can't get down with him.
一男一女想生娃 *
* When two adults wish to procreate
于是就把爱来做 *
* They lay together and copulate
男人精子一发射 *
* Male gametes, spermatozoa
女人卵子就击破 *
* Implant themselves in the ladies' ova!
一发即中 *
* Break it down!
打断一下  泡不到妞的人
I'm sorry, don't you need to actually have had sex
还能给人解释性事吗
in order to explain it?
恐龙教授还有首讲忽略恶霸的饶舌歌哦
Professor Infosaurus also has a rap about ignoring bullies.
罗宾  两性知识
Robin? Birds and bees?
我个人觉得
Well, I, for one, don't think
完全没必要教育马文两性知识
you have to teach Marvin a thing.
他如果有他爸的基因
If he's anything like his dad,
那就是天生的种马
he's a natural-born stud.
莉莉曾在黄瓜摊前
Lily got a little braggy
大大吹嘘过一番哟  "大家伙"
at a cucumber stand once, big guy.
罗宾再次获胜
Robin wins again!
-拜托  -赤裸裸的拍马屁
- Oh, come on! - That's clearly pandering!
转轮  转起来
A spin... that... wheel!
我们玩到了深夜
We played long into the night,
终于进入了最可怕的
eventually making it to the dreaded...
限时抢答环节
Lightning round!
人生第一词
First word!
横梁
Beam.
其实呢  那个叫托梁
Actually, that's a joist,
是用来承受天花板的压力
which carries the stress of the ceiling
和主体建筑重量的
versus the primary architectural load.
不过你真是我的乖孩子
But that's my boy!
书呆子
Nerd!
你真是我的乖孩子
That's my boy!
第一次为爱心碎
First heartbreak!
我知道你很伤心  小家伙
I know this hurts, little buddy,
不过以后你会有新的恋情
but you'll love again someday,
因为时间可以治疗心碎
because time will heal a broken heart.
但是治不好那小贱人的窗户
But not that bitch's window.
快逃
Run!
得了吧  我见过巴尼扔东西
Yeah, right. I've seen Barney throw.
他可不是威尼・派斯坦洛  我说得对吧
He's no Vinnie Pestano, am I right?
那个受人爱戴的印第安人棒球队中继投手啊
Beloved Indians' middle reliever.
克利夫兰的体育依然有重大意义
Cleveland sports are still relevant.
勒布朗是从哪来的  没错吧各位
LeBron who? Right, guys?
勒布朗・詹姆斯离开克利夫兰骑士加盟迈阿密热火队
泰德  你或是克利夫兰人
Ted, neither you nor Cleveland
都不懂如何忘掉抛弃你们的人
knows how to get over someone leaving them.
你处理心碎的办法估计就这样吧
Here's how you'd handle heartbreak.
振作点  小家伙
Cheer up, squirt.
外面的世界还有很多好女生
There are plenty of other wonderful women out there.
但我以为我的真命天女就是她了
But I thought that she was the one.
我要去巴尼叔叔家
I'll be at Uncle Barney's.
这太荒唐了
This is ridiculous.
我认识你们16年了
I've known you for 16 years.
我是不二的选择
I'm the obvious choice.
拜托  如果由泰德来养大他
Oh, come on, if Ted raises him,
那可怜的孩子到13岁时还会是处男
the poor kid's still gonna be a virgin when he's 13.
我才是不二的选择
I'm the obvious choice.
作为我们之中唯一有阴道的人
Hey, look, as the only one of us packing a vag,
我对照顾孩子之类的屁事有天生的本能
I got a natural instinct for nurturing and crap like that.
而且  我可以教他弓箭打猎
Plus, I can teach him how to bow hunt.
-我可以的  -我可是巴尼・斯丁森
- Yeah, I could do that. - I am Barney Stinson!
伙计们  伙计们
Guys, guys, guys!
好了  够了
Okay! All right!
很显然  你们都不懂
Obviously, none of you knows
为人父母的真正意义
what it really means to be a parent.
很显然  你们两个
Well... obviously, neither of you
再也不懂做朋友的意义
know what it means to be a friend anymore.
这话什么意思
What are you talking about?
想想吧
Think about it.
今天是这五个月来  我们跟你们俩见面时间最长的一次
This is the most we've seen you two in five months.
你们似乎对我们的生活毫不关心
You don't seem to care what's going on in our lives
只有8分或以上的事才能叫动你们
unless it's an eight or higher.
你们还想怎么样
Well, what do you expect?
-我们现在有孩子了  -是啊
- We have a baby now. - Yeah.
在麦凯伦混到打烊的日子已经结束了
The days of closing down MacLaren's are over.
除非你们想和我们一样
Unless you want to get up with us
每天早上在5点13分被宝宝的哭声吵醒
at 5:13 in the morning with a screaming baby.
就这样了吗
So that's it?
一个时代结束了  就这样吗
The... the end of an era, just like that?
听着  我们很抱歉我们没时间
Look... we're sorry if-if we don't have time
坐在酒吧里
to sit around the bar
倾听各种傻气的恋爱小问题
listening to silly little dating problems.
为人父母后
When you have a baby,
孩子不仅仅是人生中最重要的事
it's not just the most important thing in your life,
而是唯一重要的事情
it's the only important thing.
你们什么时候才能明白这点
When are you guys gonna get that?
我想我们明白了
Think we get it.
不敢相信他们就这样走了
I can't believe they just walked out.
是啊  或许这样才好
Yeah. Maybe it's for the best.
因为巴尼开始领先了
Barney was starting to pull ahead.
他们怎么能这样自私呢
I mean, how selfish can they be?
我们正努力抚养一个孩子呢
We're trying to raise a child here.
我很抱歉  我没有时间去管泰德的...
I'm sorry if I don't have time to deal with Ted's...
或是罗宾的...
um.... o-or Robin's...
或是巴尼的...
or-or Barney's...
我们将让他们其中之一做马文的教父母
You know, we were about to name one of them Marvin's godparent,
而我却不知道
and... I can't tell you
他们的生活到底过得怎么样
what's going on in any of their lives.
你觉得或许
Do you think that maybe
我们最近是没有尽到好朋友的责任吗
we've been a little crappy as friends lately?
你真的知道如何用弓箭打猎吗
Do you really know how to bow hunt?
对
Um, yeah.
在英属哥伦比亚男子军事学校里
At the British Columbia Military School for Boys
我们管这个叫"做午饭"
we called it "Making lunch."
各位
Hey, guys.
我们让米奇照顾马文
We asked Mickey to watch Marvin
这样我们可以下来聊一聊
so we could come down and talk.
我知道游戏没有结束  但是
I know that we didn't get to finish the game, but...
我们已经做出决定
we've reached a decision.
莉莉
Lily?
我们决定
We've decided...
撤销"8分或以上"规定
...to revoke the "Eight or higher" Rule.
什么
What?
我们想知道你们生活中的一切
We want to know everything that's going on with you guys.
真的吗
Really?
你们是我们最好的朋友
You're our best friends.
所有事都是8分或以上
Everything is an eight or higher.
那晚是半年来第一次
And for the first time in almost half a year,
莉莉和马修在麦凯伦待到打烊
Lily and Marshall closed down MacLaren's.
总之
Anyway,
维多利亚的父亲和我研究出了支付方法
Victoria's dad and I are working out a payment plan
利息率相当的合理
with a very reasonable interest rate.
至少  尼克的摩托是省油型的
At least, Nick's cycle is fuel-efficient--
我们最快飙到了30  或35英里的时速呢
we're getting, like,30, 35 miles to the cob.
-是嘛  -没错
- Really? - Yeah.
我应该早点告诉你们那个6.5分的
You know, I should've told you about that six and a half sooner.
巴尼・斯丁森上了一个低于8分的
Barney Stinson banging anything less than an eight?
这事绝对值15分
That's like a 15.
那晚很棒
And it was a great night.
直到
Until...
早上5点13分
继续睡吧
Go back to bed.
我们来处理
We got this.
莉莉和马修最终决定了监护人人选
And Lily and Marshall finally decided on a guardian.
-你确定吗  宝贝  -是的
- Are you sure about this, baby? - Yes.
无论发生什么事  我希望马文与家人在一起
No matter what happens, I want Marvin to stay in the family.
泰德・莫斯比  罗宾・特布罗斯基  巴尼・斯丁森